# ANDRÉS BONILLA FULL STACK DEVELOPER

# ABOUT ME

As a Full Stack Developer, I'm comfortable working in both English and Spanish, enabling me to collaborate effectively in multicultural environments.

In addition to my technical skills, I also have experience in leadership, planning, teamwork and the use of methodologies like Scrum.

I have a great capacity for adaptability and I am open to learn new technologies and working methodologies.

# PROJECTS

# Match Maker - Balloon Group Argentina

Mobile app to organise competitions, create leagues and manage scores.

#### **Guitar React**

Online store where a wide selection of electric guitars are offered as main product.

#### **Movie BASE**

Website developed by consuming the TMDB API.

### EXPERIENCE

# 2021 - 2022 Germany

Thanks to the boom of the delivery sector in Berlin, I had the chance to work as a delivery driver for two major e-commerce companies, Take Away and Delivery Hero.

#### 2019 - 2021 New Zealand

I moved to New Zealand with the goal of expand my horizons and learn a new language. During my time there, I worked for over 10 companies in various roles, ranging from cherry picking and pine tree pollination to serving as the direct assistant to the area manager in a cake factory.

#### 2014 - 2019 Uruguay

As an education professional, I taught programming, computer logic, and mathematics at UTU (public education). It was a rewarding experience where I contributed to the technical and personal growth of young people with a strong focus on computer science.



- in linkedin.../andresbonilla-dev
- github.../andres-bonilla
- x.andresbonilla@gmail.com

# LANGUAGES

 Spanish English

# STACK

- React
- HTML
- Redux
- CSS
- React Router Sass
- React Native Sequelize
- Expo
- SQLite
- Node.js
- PostgreSQL
- Express
- MongoDB
- Axios
- Mongoose
- Git
- JWT

- JavaScript
- Passport.js
- TypeScript
- Docker

#### EDUCATION

# **Full Stack Developer** Plataforma 5

Technical skills training with a comprehensive focus on soft skills development.

# **Computer Engineering UdelaR - Fing**

Studied up to the second year, with special emphasis on data structures.

**B.Sc.** in Mathematics and Physics **UdelaR - Fcien** 

First year completed.